MOHPREET KAUR

mohpreet.kaur8@gmail.com ◆ Cell +1 249-288-7290 ◆ LinkedIn

CAREER SUMMARY

Experience 4 months Co-op as a Data and Analytics Technician

2+ years in Direct Sales.

Languages MS SQL, My SQL, DAX, Power Query Language M

Tools Visual Studio, SQL Workbench, SSMS, Azure, PowerBI, Microsoft Suite, Google

Workspace, Salesforce

Portfolio Used JavaScript, CSS3, HTML5 (Animations, Media Queries, Responsive design)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Easy Financial

Mississauga, ON

Sales Admin - Pilot 08/2022 - Present

Technologies: Salesforce, WealthView, Excel

• Built a Sales tracker for better achievement of monthly individual targets.

- Managing the Loan Applications started online and assigning them to the Agents.
- Working with Salesforce Data to produce daily Outbound Dial List.
- Analyzing the work done on applications and reporting the Leadership with potential compliance issue.

Financial Services Representative

03/2022 - 07/2022

- Improved the Personal Sales numbers by 200+% in the first 3 months of starting.
- One of the Top performers in the Sales of Ancillary Products.

Regional Municipality of York

Newmarket, ON

09/2021 - 12/2021

Data and Analytics Technician **Technologies**: PowerBI, DAX, M

- Successfully reworked and launched the Region's Hospital Performance Dashboard providing the user 70% more information expanding from 4 Sheets to around 9 interlinked sheets.
- Increased the report interactivity and organized the data in a more logical order.
- Set up the report for automatic refreshes for timely and efficient updates.

EDUCATION

Undergraduate Diploma in Computer Programming

Barrie, ON

Georgian College

01/2021 - 12/2021

- Secured overall GPA of 96.37/100 with Dean's List
- International Student Leadership Award & Board of Governor's Medal Award

JavaScript Courses - Self-Learning

Remote - 2021

Modern JS Features – Classes, Promise, Arrow Functions, Variables (let, const, var), Array Methods, De-structuring, Modules, Ternary Operator, Spread Operator, Logical assignment operators

ACCREDITATIONS

REMIC Mortgage Agent

06/2022 - 07/2022

• Licensed as Ontario Mortgage Agent with an ability to work on Secured Loan Applications for the Province of Ontario.